[
  {
    "id" : 1,
    "question" : "What's the point of going out? We're just gonna wind up back here anyway.",
    "answer" : "Homer",
    "asked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question" : "My eyes. The goggles do nothing.",
    "answer" : "Radioactive Man",
    "asked": false
  },
   {
    "id" : 3,
    "question" : "How old is Hans Moleman",
    "answer" : "31",
    "asked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question" : "There's only one thing to do at a moment like this: strut!",
    "answer" : "Bart",
    "asked": false
  },
   {
    "id" : 5,
    "question" : "I, for one, welcome our new insect overlords.",
    "answer" : "Kent Brockman",
    "asked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question" : "Loneliness and cheeseburgers are a dangerous mix.",
    "answer" : "Comic Book Guy",
    "asked": false
  },
   {
    "id" : 7,
    "question" : "They taste like burning",
    "answer" : "ralph wiggum",
    "asked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question" : "My eyes. The goggles do nothing.",
    "answer" : "Radioactive Man",
    "asked": false
  },
   {
    "id" : 9,
    "question" : "You tried your best and you failed miserably. The lesson is: Never try.",
    "answer" : "Homer",
    "asked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question" : "Don’t make me run. I’m full of chocolate.",
    "answer" : "Uter",
    "asked": false
  },
   {
    "id" : 11,
    "question" : "I'd rather let thousands of guilty men go free then to chase them",
    "answer" : "Chief wiggum",
    "asked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question" : "Go out on a Tuesday? Who am I, Charlie Sheen?",
    "answer" : "Marge",
    "asked": false
  }
]

